[{"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/日历.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/汽水瓶.svg", "type": "cylinder"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/文件夹.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_1.svg", "type": "cylinder"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/汽水瓶.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/日历.svg", "type": "cuboid"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 1], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/饮料瓶.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/手机.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "type": "orb"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 1], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_1.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/书本_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/手电筒_1.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/手机.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg", "type": "orb"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/手机.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/汽水瓶.svg", "type": "cylinder"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 0], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/手电筒_1.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/文件夹.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg", "type": "orb"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/文件夹.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/汽水瓶.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg", "type": "orb"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/手电筒_1.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/书本_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/手机.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/汽水瓶.svg", "type": "cylinder"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/文件夹.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/汽水瓶.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "type": "orb"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/饮料瓶.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/手机.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg", "type": "orb"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/汽水瓶.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/日历.svg", "type": "cuboid"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 1], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/手电筒_1.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/书本_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "type": "orb"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，你能帮他们选择合适的包装盒吗？", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/男孩/8.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "type": "orb"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/手电筒_1.svg", "type": "cylinder"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/日历.svg", "type": "cuboid"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg", "type": "cube"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}, {"src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_1.svg", "type": "cuboid"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect2"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的特征"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-6-6-04"}]